const DATA = {
    questions: [
      {
        prompt: "Which company invented the first smartphone?",
        options: [
          "Apple",
          "Nokia",
          "IBM",
          "Motorola"
        ],
        answer:  "IBM"
      },

      {
        prompt: "Which prestigious university did Microsoft founder Bill Gates drop out of?",
        options: [
          "Yale University",
          "Harvard University",
          "Stanford University",
          "Columbia University"
        ],
        answer:  "Harvard University"
      },

      {
        prompt: "What does LG stand for in LG Electronics?",
        options: [ 
          "Little Giants",
          "Light Goods",
          "Logical Gaming",
          "Lucky Goldstar"
        ],
        answer:  "Lucky Goldstar"
      },

      {
        prompt: "What does CPU stand for?",
        options: [ 
          "Central Processing Unit",
          "Computer Process Unit",
          "Call Packets User-Interface",
          "Cold Punch Utilities"
        ],
        answer:  "Central Processing Unit"
      },

      {
        prompt: "What year did the first Apple iPhone launch?",
        options: [ 
           "2000",
           "2006",
           "2007",
           "2005"
        ],
        answer:  "2007"
      },

      {
        prompt: "What is the name of Elon Muskâ€™s aerospace company?",
        options: [ 
          "Tesla",
          "Starlink",
          "SpaceX",
          "Hyperloop"
        ],
        answer:  "SpaceX"
      },
      
      {
        prompt: "Created in 1990, what was the name of the first internet search engine?",
        options: [ 
          "Internet Explorer",
          "Google",
          "Archie",
          "Yahoo"
        ],
        answer:  "Archie"
      },

      {
        prompt: "Originally Amazon only sold which product?",
        options: [ 
          "Packing materials",
          "Books",
          "School supplies",
          "Appliances"
        ],
        answer:  "Books"
      },

      {
        prompt: "Given the rise of search engines, what does SEO stand for?",
        options: [ 
          "Style Each Optimization",
          "Search Engine Operation",
          "Signal Engine Operations",
          "Search Engine Optimization"
        ],
        answer:  "Search Engine Optimization"
      },

      {
        prompt: "Facebook co-founder Sean Parker was also the co-founder of which company?",
        options: [ 
          "Instagram",
          "Napster",
          "MySpace",
          "Twitter"
        ],
        answer:  "Napster"
      },

      {
        prompt: "Asus and Acer announced that they would stop making what products in 2013?",
        options: [ 
          "Smart phones",
          "Microwaves",
          "Tablets",
          "Netbooks"
        ],
        answer:  "Netbooks"
      },

      {
        prompt: "Introduced in 1993, what was Apple's first tablet computer?",
        options: [ 
          "Newton MessagePad",
          "Apple Pad",
          "Idea pad",
          "iPad"
        ],
        answer:  "Newton MessagePad"
      },

      {
        prompt: "What company did the founders of YouTube work for before starting up YouTube?",
        options: [
           "McDonalds",
          "Ebay",
          "PayPal",
          "Google"
        ],
        answer:  "PayPal"
      },

      {
        prompt: "Where is Microsoft's headquarters?",
        options: [ 
          "Silicon Valley, California",
          "Redmond, Washington",
          "Portland, Oregon",
          "Seattle, Washington"
        ],
        answer:  "Redmond, Washington"
      },

      {
        prompt: "What is an employee who works for Google called?",
        options: [
          "Employee",
          "Pixalators",
          "Googler",
          "Googles"
        ],
        answer:  "Googler"
      }
    ],
    currentQuestionIndex: 0,
    score: 0
  };